我们已经花了很长时间去创建一个ContentProvider
We've spent a long time building a content provider.
但是  我们仅仅是简单的
But, we are only using it just enough for
测试一下ContentProvider的功能效果
us to test that we got the content provider working.
当请求数据库的时候  这些类是这样用的
When we query the database, here's how these classes are used.
我们的UI首先使用WeatherContract创建一个URI
Our UI, first, builds a URI, using the weathercontract.
这个UI然后使用通过这个UI调用ContentResolver里的一个方法
The UI then uses this UI to call a method in the Content Resolver.
这个方法会将请求最终转向WeatherProvider
Which ultimately forwards the request to our WeatherProvider.
WeatherProvider通过WeatherDBHelpter
Our WeatherProvider uses Weather DB Helper
获得SQLite数据库的实例
to get an instance of SQLite Database.
创建或者更新数据库表也是有必要的
Creating, or updating the tables of our database is necessary.
然后我们将SQL的请求传入SQLiteDatabase类
We then pass the SQL query to the SQLiteDatabase class,
SQLiteDatabase会将请求最终发送给SQLite数据库
which sends our query off to our SQLite database.
CursorLoader拿到URI
Cursor Loader takes the URI, and
代替我们在AsyncTask中调用ContentResolver
calls the Content Resolver on our behalf, inside of an AsyncTask.
最终  cursor会返回到Android UI里
Ultimately, the cursor gets returned to the Android UI,
数据库Cursor会在Sunshine中被CursorAdatper
and it will be used by a cursor adapter, to populate the list view,
用来填充ListView
in Sunshine from our database cursor.
和我们使用arrayAdapter填充listview类似
Similar to the way our array adapter populated the list view from an array.
我们下一个任务  就是用cursorAdapter替换掉
For our next task, we are going to replace the array adapter,
forecastFragment里的arrayAdapter
we have currently in forecast fragment, with a cursor adapter.
我们最终会使用CursorLoader将cursorAdapter和数据库关联起来
We'll eventually connect it to our database using a cursor loader.